Friends, today again I welcome you all
and friends, today we will
discuss about ICICI group of shares,
especially ICICI Bank, ICICI
Prudential, ICICI
Securities and ICICI Lombard
and also friends, we will
try to find out the target price and stoploss and
which share can give better returns in this falling market and
which city can be visited for long-term or short term,
we will tell you the slide bracelet by investing in its date, so
friends, watch the entire video, the
answer will be seen,
we will address from different angles
and friends, if you
want to do intraday trading, then join our Telegram channels, the
link of which is
given in the description box and anyone has to
open a demat account which will be
very useful in IPO allotment, right now this year,
from January itself, a lot of IPOs are going to come, so
if you have a demat account of any bank, whether it is
for sewerage and you want to stop trading or for
stocks, then definitely open a demat account, so
friends, let's  People discuss
about these three shares and four cities,
so first of all we find out the latest news,
what is the latest news about all these
seniors of ICICI group,
so friends, the biggest news that is coming out is
that Infosys, Bharti Airtel, Airtel,
ICICI Bank and top large cap
stocks to buy on financial year did not agree
wife, so as per the results that are coming,
Infosys results have come,
Bharti Airtel, ICICI Bank results are
yet to come, so according to that there
is improvement and according to that the performance is good, looking at that the
return on equity and if you see, if
you want to see the share for one year
and then
ICICI Bank has turned the level in terms of loan no department, so definitely friends,
this can be your first pick, second
friends, please share ICICI Prudential Life
Insurance, it has
given buy rating, target price 630 has been
looted for one year, thirdly,
ICICI Lombard's father husband is on the cent
of the total business on the next  325
wasted so with the chance of growth counter question
ICICI Lombard is a unique type of
company which is very aggressive in general insurance
and is performing very well
and at the same time friends it is an excellent
quality stock and it is also inbuilt so
somewhere or take the
help of machine learning so wherever
technology is used then it is definitely doing
well and the
target price given by Khan for this share is 1710 for
one year ICICI Securities has given a target price of 1710 for
free treatment and
health body it is the front runner on
digital initiative so definitely friends
all the shares have positive news and all are
good quality shares so right now we can see
which share is performing better among the comparative ones
so if you are able to see the chart
then at the current level you can see
ICICI Bank and ICICI
Prudential and ICICI Lombard General
Insurance ic-34 if you are watching from here friends
here if you see this place
currently then continuously ICICI  This is our
price of 19th October given here and
if you look at the current price level, then
how the top moment has come from pearl water, in
it the
share of ICICI Bank has run the most
in the last three months and after that the share which has run is
ICICI Lombard Bank
ICICI Prudential Dena ICICI
Securities, the share has lost a lot of shine right now,
so definitely friends, there is a lot of room in this too to
go up and all the
four stocks are of very good quality, now
friends we will do stark lip and
you can see the Nifty data here friends,
so ICICI Securities
hit a high of 568, similarly the bank
hit a high of 561, ICICI Prudential Dena 538, such a share of
Lambodar 1626, the top has corrected well from the level,
especially
ICICI Lombard ICICI
Securities, so if you look at the Nifty data, the
delivery of both these shares
is also fine and at the same time the  Harris pressure is also
very low, so first pick. If we talk on this data, then
definitely ICICI Lombard is
the first pick and danger ICICI
Securities. Like both these shares.
Definitely friends, here you can
expect to see returns of up to 20%.
ICICI Bank and ICICI
Prudential are also very good quality staff
members. If there is a slight correction then you can
enter in it. So
friends, let's discuss that if
someone has a current position, then
what will be the stop loss for three months and what will be the target
price. The price is sister's house. If we
look at the current price level, then the uptrend that we have placed there is
500 thirteen, so if
we make this the stop loss of 531, then
stay with the stop loss of 513. And the
earlier targets above will also be
565, then we can stick to the target of 565.
Rs 550 is dedicating that it
is neutral, 9 is enough, no what should be the limit.  It is definitely
close to the hotel, so friends, one
can go here by bike, but the share market which is
at a very high and is correcting,
so some correction can also come in this, ICICI Bank is
also from the list, so definitely, a little
correction can come in this also, even then
maintain the stoploss of 513 and stay put,
if you see ICICI Prudential Life,
here also it is neutral
and if you are seeing here, the
share is standing at the price level of 500,
around one and a half inch, so its major support was
placed at 4068, so you put a stoploss of 473
here for bringing it to the front lower
and the target on the upside is 530, the
first target will be achieved, so from here
with the 473th target stoploss, the target of 530 has been
achieved,
that the share of ICICI Securities has
not moved much and is demanding a lot of range,
it has backed like a sideways chart, so
friends, on the day this  It will trade 467
definitely friends, there has been
no volume for a long time, very good quality staff,
the day the volume in it is Sanjay 500 level
which you are seeing here, it can be
seen here, if it is seen at this level also at the fiber
level, then you have a very small
stop loss, bike on the strength of the current
and put a stop loss of 425 in it and on the upside you can
see the target of 500, as per the
method, ASI is very
close to the should not, so definitely you can bike at this level,
if you see the share price target of all
three-four, then like this bank
ICICI Prudential ICICI
Lombard ICICI Securities, then
look at these three-four shares, the showing
level is Odh Security, bike it at the current level
and ICICI Lombard has also
come very close to the label field, so keep trading these two shares
and while
maintaining the stop loss, target price, definitely you can get a
return of ten to twenty percent from here with
free close, follow us on
Telegram  It is known as day trading balls. You
must read the day trading display on Twitter and Facebook and definitely place your target price
and stop loss and do
your lip before any investment.
We do this only for educational purposes, it has nothing to do
with investment. The
time you friends